<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--
 - MIT License
 -
 - Copyright (c) 2021 Gourav Khunger
 -
 - Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
 - of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
 - in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
 - to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
 - copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
 - furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
 -
 - The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
 - copies or substantial portions of the Software.
 -
 - THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
 - IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
 - FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
 - AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
 - LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
 - OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
 - SOFTWARE.
 -->

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">JekyllEx</string>
    <string name="website_url">https://jekyllex.xyz</string>
    <string name="docs_url">https://docs.jekyllex.xyz</string>

    <string name="gh_repo_url">https://github.com/jekyllex/jekyllex-android</string>
    <string name="issues_url">https://github.com/jekyllex/jekyllex-android/issues/new</string>

    <string name="com_auth0_domain">jekyllex.us.auth0.com</string>
    <string name="com_auth0_scheme">jekyllex</string>

    <string name="website">Website</string>
    <string name="github_repository">Github Repository</string>
    <string name="docs">JekyllEx Docs</string>
    <string name="share">Share JekyllEx</string>
    <string name="authenticate">Authenticate</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="profile_picture">Profile Picture</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="loading_msg">Loading your repositories…</string>
    <string name="no_connection">No Internet Connection Available</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="go_back">Go Back</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="markdown_editor">Markdown Editor</string>
    <string name="select_repo_message">
        Here\'s the list of your repositories, choose one or search
        for the repository that has your jekyll blog in it.
    </string>
    <string name="posts">Posts</string>
    <string name="login_msg">Please log-in with your GitHub account to start using JekyllEx</string>
    <string name="no_posts_found">No \"_posts\" folder found in this repository</string>
    <string name="editor_et_hint">Click here to start writing</string>
    <string name="preview">Preview Changes</string>
    <string name="edit_meta">Edit Meta Data</string>
    <string name="alert_et_msg">Add post\'s Meta-Data here…</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="metadata_editor">Meta Data Editor</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="upload_post">Upload Post</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="commit_message">Commit Message</string>
    <string name="enter_commit_message">Enter Commit Message</string>
    <string name="upload">Upload</string>
    <string name="working">Working on it…</string>
    <string name="repo_private">Private</string>
    <string name="repo_archived">Archived</string>
    <string name="open_in_browser">Open in Browser</string>
    <string name="built_with"><![CDATA[Built with: <b>%1$s</b>.]]></string>
    <string name="file_size"><![CDATA[File size: <b>%1$s</b>.]]></string>
    <string name="written_on"><![CDATA[Written on: <b>%1$s</b>.]]></string>
    <string name="new_post">New Post</string>
    <string name="create">Create</string>
    <string name="enter_new_post_filename">Enter New Post\'s Filename</string>
    <string name="file_name_example"><![CDATA[Example:<br /><b>2021–08–22-my-awesome-post.md</b>]]></string>
    <string name="report_msg">Report a bug/issue</string>
    <string name="edit_file">Edit File</string>
    <string name="preview_changes">Preview Changes</string>
    <string name="followers">Followers</string>
    <string name="following">Following</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="uid">uid: %1$s</string>
    <string name="refresh_profile">Refresh Profile</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="tnc">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="share_text">
        Hey, Check out JekyllEx- The easiest way to manage your jekyll blog
        directly from your android device \n\n
        https://jekyllex.xyz
    </string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_text">
        <![CDATA[
Gourav Khunger built the JekyllEx app as an Open Source app.
This SERVICE is provided by Gourav Khunger at no cost and is intended for use as is.
\n\n
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and
disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
\n\n
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information
in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and
improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described
in this Privacy Policy.
\n\n
The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions,
which is accessible at JekyllEx unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.
\n\n
**Information Collection and Use**
\n\n
For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain
personally identifiable information. The information that I request will be retained on your
device and is not collected by me in any way.
\n\n
The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.
\n\n
Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app
\n\n
*   [Google Analytics for Firebase](https://firebase.google.com/policies/analytics) \n
*   [Firebase Crashlytics](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/)
\n\n
**Log Data**
\n\n
I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I
collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data.
\n\n
This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address,
device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service,
the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.
\n\n
**Cookies**
\n\n
Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique
identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored
on your device\'s internal memory.
\n\n
This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party
code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services.
You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent
to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of
this Service.
\n\n
**Service Providers**
\n\n
I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:
\n\n
*   To facilitate our Service; \n
*   To provide the Service on our behalf; \n
*   To perform Service-related services; or \n
*   To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. \n
*   To provide the Service on our behalf; \n
\n
I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal
Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they
are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
\n\n
**Security**
\n\n
I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use
commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission
over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot
guarantee its absolute security.
\n\n
**Links to Other Sites**
\n\n
This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be
directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me.
Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites.
I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies,
or practices of any third-party sites or services.
\n\n
**Children’s Privacy**
\n\n
These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. I do not knowingly collect personally
identifiable information from children under 13 years of age. In the case I discover that a
child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our
servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with
personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.
\n\n
**Changes to This Privacy Policy**
\n\n
I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page
periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy
on this page.
\n\n
This policy is effective as of **2021-08-26**
\n\n
**Contact Us**
\n\n
If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me
at [gouravkhunger18@gmail.com](mailto:gouravkhunger18@gmail.com).
      ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="tnc_text">
        <![CDATA[
By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should
make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to
copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or our trademarks in any way.
\n\n
You shouldn’t try to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative versions.
If you wish to do so, that should be done on the github repository of this project by
making pull requests.
\n
The app itself, and all the trade marks, copyright, database rights and other intellectual
property rights related to it, still belong to Gourav Khunger.
\n\n
Gourav Khunger is committed to ensuring that the app is as useful and efficient as possible.
For that reason, we reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for its services,
at any time and for any reason. We will never charge you for the app or its services without
making it very clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.
\n\n
The JekyllEx app stores and processes personal data that you have provided to us, in order
to provide my Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your phone and access to the app secure.
We therefore recommend that you do not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of
removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the official operating system of your
device. It could make your phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs,
compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean that the JekyllEx app won’t work
properly or at all.
\n\n
The app does use third party services that declare their own Terms and Conditions.
\n\n
Link to Terms and Conditions of third party service providers used by the app
\n\n
*   [Google Analytics for Firebase](https://firebase.google.com/terms/analytics) \n
*   [Firebase Crashlytics](https://firebase.google.com/terms/crashlytics)
\n\n
You should be aware that there are certain things that Gourav Khunger will not take
responsibility for. Certain functions of the app will require the app to have an active
internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi, or provided by your mobile network provider,
but Gourav Khunger cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full functionality if
you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t have any of your data allowance left.
\n\n
If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you should remember that your terms of
the agreement with your mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may be charged
by your mobile provider for the cost of data for the duration of the connection while accessing
the app, or other third party charges. In using the app, you’re accepting responsibility for any
such charges, including roaming data charges if you use the app outside of your home territory
(i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming.
If you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re using the app, please be aware
that we assume that you have received permission from the bill payer for using the app.
\n\n
Along the same lines, Gourav Khunger cannot always take responsibility for the way you use the
app i.e. You need to make sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of battery and
you can’t turn it on to avail the Service, Gourav Khunger cannot accept responsibility.
\n\n
With respect to Gourav Khunger’s responsibility for your use of the app, when you’re using the
app, it’s important to bear in mind that although we endeavour to ensure that it is updated and
correct at all times, we do rely on third parties to provide information to us so that we can
make it available to you. Gourav Khunger accepts no liability for any loss, direct or indirect,
you experience as a result of relying wholly on this functionality of the app.
\n\n
At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is currently available on Android – the
requirements for system(and for any additional systems we decide to extend the availability of the
app to) may change, and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep using the app.
Gourav Khunger does not promise that it will always update the app so that it is relevant to you
and/or works with the Android version that you have installed on your device. However, you promise
to always accept updates to the application when offered to you, We may also wish to stop providing
the app, and may terminate use of it at any time without giving notice of termination to you.
Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the rights and licenses granted to you
in these terms will end; (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it from your device.
\n\n
**Changes to This Terms and Conditions**
\n\n
I may update our Terms and Conditions from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this
page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new
Terms and Conditions on this page.
\n\n
These terms and conditions are effective as of **2021-08-26**
\n\n
**Contact Us**
\n\n
If you have any questions or suggestions about my Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to
contact me at [gouravkhunger18@gmail.com](mailto:gouravkhunger18@gmail.com).
]]>
    </string>

    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="font_header">App Font</string>
    <string name="colour_header">Colour Settings</string>

    <!-- Font Preferences -->
    <string name="font_title">Default Font</string>

    <!-- Color Preferences -->
    <string name="primary_app_color_title">Primary App Color</string>
    <string name="primary_text_color_title">Primary Text Color</string>

    <string name="previous">Previous</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="enter_repo_name">Enter repo name</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
</resources>